TOM STÖCKLEIN

Seeking new opportunities.

stoecklein@gmail.com

Summary

At Demand Media, Thomas focused on identifying and analyzing various potential investment opportunities, acquisitions, and strategic partnerships. Prior to Demand Media, Thomas was a Senior Analyst at Covert & Co., where he focused on the execution of M&A and financing transactions including financial modeling, due diligence, presentation development and industry research. Prior to Covert & Co., Thomas was an analyst at Cappello Capital, a generalist M&A, capital markets, and restructuring advisory firm based in Los Angeles. Prior to joining Cappello, he worked as an analyst at ARCIS Capital in Paris and London. At ARCIS, a private equity secondaries fund with \$1 billion in assets under management, he focused on analyzing and executing potential investments in limited partnership fund interests of private equity partnerships. Thomas graduated with a B.A. in International Relations and a minor in Classics from the University of Southern California. During his time at USC, Thomas was part of the Mock Trial Team and also served as a mentor to high school students in disadvantaged neighborhoods through the Teach International Relations Program. Thomas is a member of the German American Business Association (GABA), a member-driven non-profit organization that fosters transatlantic knowledge-sharing and networking among German-American and Californian business and tech communities. Specialties: • Financial Analysis and Valuation • Mergers & Acquisitions • Private Placements of Equity and Debt • Private Equity Secondaries • Strategic Advisory • Due Diligence

Experience

Corporate Development (Contract) at Demand Media

October 2014 - February 2015 (5 months)

Demand Media, Inc. (NYSE: DMD) is a leading digital content and media and domain services company that informs and entertains one of the internet's largest audiences, helps advertisers find innovative ways to engage with their customers and enables publishers to expand their online presence. Headquartered in Santa Monica, CA, Demand Media has offices in North America, South America and Europe.

1 recommendation available upon request

Senior Analyst, Tech and Media Investment Banking at Covert & Co.

January 2014 - October 2014 (10 months)

The Covert & Co. team has experience with more than 100 M&A and financing transactions with companies including Google, Yahoo, News Corp, Walt Disney, Comcast, eBay, IAC, Viacom, CBS, MySpace, IBM, Cisco, Meebo, SAP and Microsoft

1 recommendation available upon request

Analyst, Investment Banking at Cappello Capital Corp.

January 2012 - January 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Cappello Capital Corp. is a boutique investment banking firm that offers corporate finance advisory services. The firm provides mergers and acquisitions, recapitalizations, restructuring, and private placement advisory services. Additionally, it offers merchant banking and consulting services. Cappello Capital Corp. was founded in 1992 and is based in Santa Monica, California.

5 recommendations available upon request

Analyst, Private Equity Secondaries at ARCIS Capital Ltd

September 2010 - November 2011 (1 year 3 months)

ARCIS is an independent secondary fund specialising in the purchase of positions in private equity funds and portfolios of private equity backed companies from investors seeking liquidity. ARCIS' founders were pioneers in the secondary market for private equity assets both in the US and Europe and have been active players since 1984. ARCIS has successfully executed more than 200 secondary transactions, comprising over 500 positions purchased in over 250 funds and portfolios of private equity backed companies.

Skills & Expertise

Private Equity

Investment Banking

Valuation

Mergers & Acquisitions

Due Diligence

Financial Modeling

Strategy

Investments

Financial Analysis

Finance

Equities

Portfolio Management

Venture Capital

Start-ups

Private Placements

Capital

Competitive Analysis

Entrepreneurship

Strategic Planning

Mergers

Investor Relations

Capital IQ

LBO

Working Capital Management

Corporate Finance

Teamwork

Team Motivation

Cross-functional Team Leadership

Series 63

SaaS

Product Management

Pitch Development

HTML5

JavaScript

CSS

Responsive Web Design

Front-end Development

Languages

English

(Native or bilingual proficiency)

German

(Native or bilingual proficiency)

Education

University of Southern California

B.A., International Relations, 2007 - 2010

1 recommendation available upon request

Chandler/Gilbert Community College

A.A., Business, Liberal Arts, 2006 - 2007

Udacity

Nanodegree, Front-End Web Development, 2015

TOM STÖCKLEIN

Seeking new opportunities.

stoecklein@gmail.com



8 people have recommended TOM

"I worked with Thomas at Demand Media where we spent a significant amount of time together on corporate development initiatives. He has a real passion for digital media and his knowledge of the landscape is an asset. He understands well how to think about strategic implications of acquisitions and divestitures, and especially what that means for a digital media company."

— Travis Page, managed TOM

"Thomas was a valuable member of the Covert & Co. team. His professionalism and strong work ethic were always greatly appreciated, along with his enthusiasm, integrity and strong investment banking skills. I would strongly recommend Thomas and hope that we have the opportunity to work together again in the future."

— **Kevin Covert**, managed TOM

"Having Thomas be part of my team has been a pleasure. He conducts himself with integrity. Thomas can be counted on not just to work hard, but to represent the company in a positive light. His strong work ethic is accompanied by his analytical problem-solving skills and his entrepreneurial, innovative spirit. Thomas continually demonstrates a strong desire for learning and professional growth. This translates into meaningful contributions and excellent work products. His strong team working skills allow him to create a productive environment of trust and accountability. Thomas is very attentive to requests by senior staff and gets the job done. In addition, his international experience and professional demeanor make him a well-rounded individual, who would make an invaluable contribution to any organization. Alexander L Cappello Chairmen & CEO Cappello Group, Inc."

— Alexander Cappello, Chairman, Cappello Group,inc., managed TOM at Cappello Capital Corp.

"Thomas has a one of a kind work ethic that is evident through his ability to focus on small details while understanding the big picture of complex financial situations. He has always given 100% to every project we were engaged on together and was liked by all. Thomas is not only capable of solving difficult problems, he is a leader by nature and has a strong track record of exceeding expectations set forth by senior executives."

— Mark Dru, MBA Spring Associate, Cappello Capital Corp., worked directly with TOM at Cappello Capital Corp.

"Thomas is a pleasure to work with and i would highly recommend him for an analyst role."

— Artin Sedighan, Senior Associate, Cappello Capital Corp., managed TOM at Cappello Capital Corp.

"Thomas is a self starter with natural qualitative and quantitave ability. He brings a maturity and professionalism to his work product and demeanor not often found at his level. Thomas will make a great addition to any Investment Banking firm or other professional organization."

— Clay Bryan, VP, Cappello Capital Corp., managed TOM at Cappello Capital Corp.

"I came to know Thomas several years ago through a family friend. Upon meeting him for the first time, I knew there was something special about this young man. I had been in the construction industry for decades, working up through the trades and into a high profile executive role in capital portfolio management in the NYC markets where good talent competes in large numbers. I had several years of hands on managing the growth of our corporate market share in property acquisitions and development in Manhattan and the surrounding Tri-State area which put me in the catbird seat with respect to locating and on-boarding talent to help us achieve our targeted objectives. I interviewed candidates every Friday for years and developed a pretty good sense for recognizing talented people. If I found someone that I thought had great potential and I didn't have the position for them at the moment, I would create a new business angle and on-board them asap. Good people are hard to come by and harder to keep. Thomas is one of those good people with a rare set of abilities paired with an outstanding perspective. I am now a disabled and retired cancer survivor or I would be creating a business niche for Thomas to ply his abilities in what would be a sure winner. I strongly recommend Thomas to you as a potential asset to any business management endeavor you may have or are considering. You would only benefit by connecting to this young man at the earliest opportunity. He will surprise you with his eager yet strategic approach to succeeding in business and wiser than his young age might portend. Sincerely, Dennis Taylor dtaylormesa@gmail.com"

— **Dennis Taylor**, managed TOM indirectly

"I coached Thomas on the undergraduate mock trial team at U.S.C. He was always very eager to learn and one of the hardest workers on the team, even to this day. He is one of the most diligent and hardworking people I have known, personally or professionally."

— **Hooman Kazemi**, Faculty Lecturer, Dept. of Political Science, University of Southern California, taught TOM at University of Southern California

Contact TOM on LinkedIn